{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher Haven",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Ashland Craft",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 13,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice is an American reality television singing competition broadcast on NBC. It premiered on April 26, 2011, and is based on the original The Voice of Holland of 2010, created by",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher Haven",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Ashland Craft",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Ashley Bryant",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Asher HaVon",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US 2022 winner is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2019 is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner is Jershika Maple.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice 2022 winner is Bryce Leatherwood.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Javier Colon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner 2022 is Carter Rubin.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner 2021 is Jershika Maple.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US 2022 winner is Girl Named Tom.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Javier Colon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Camila Cabello.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Camila Cabello.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US 2022 is Carter Rubin.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US this year is Jordan Smith.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US 2022 winner is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2019 is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner 2022 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Brynn Cartelli.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner is Brynn Cartelli.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US 2020 is Jershika Maple.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US is going to be Brynn Cartelli.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is Jake Hoot.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US is Brynn Cartelli.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner is going to be announced on the show's official website.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Irrelevant Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice US winner is not yet known.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner 2023 is Carter Rubin.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The Voice winner 2023 is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "The winner of The Voice US is Maelyn Jarmon.",
            "needle": "The winner of The Voice US this year has not been announced yet, as this season is still ongoing.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "Who was the winner of The Voice US this year?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}